Over 200 years ago, much of what we know
200 多年前，我们今天所知的
as the American Midwest appeared to be
美国中西部的大部分地区似乎正朝着
on a trajectory towards becoming part of
成为加拿大一部分的方向发展
Canada. Once known as the Old Northwest,
。
this vast region stretched from the area
这片广袤的地区曾被称为旧西北地区，从
north of the Ohio River to the east of
俄亥俄河以北一直延伸到
the Mississippi River. At this time, it
密西西比河以东。 当时，它
wasn't American at all and was instead
根本不属于美国，而是在《
Quebec Act, which significantly expanded
魁北克法案》签署后，由英国魁北克省控制。该法案极大地扩展了
Britain's borders deep into the North
英国的疆界，使其深入
American continent. But that creates the
北美大陆。 但这又引出了一个
question, why didn't the Midwest become
问题：为什么美国中西部没有成为
a part of Canada? Why was it handed to
加拿大的一部分？ 为什么会把它交给
the newly formed United States? And how
新成立的美国？
close did we come to seeing a vastly
我们距离在地图上看到一个
different version of North America on
截然不同的北美版本究竟有多近
maps? In 1773, Canada didn't exist as a
？  1773 年，加拿大还没有作为一个
country just yet, but a major part of
国家存在，但
the land we associate [music] with it
我们今天与音乐联系在一起的大部分土地当时
was primarily within the British colony
主要位于被
known as the province of Quebec.
称为魁北克省的英国殖民地境内。
Britain had gained control of these
英国
defeating France in the Seven Years War,
在七年战争中击败法国后，控制了这些北美领土，
inheriting not just land, but lucrative
不仅继承了土地，还继承了利润丰厚的
trade routes and beneficial alliances.
贸易路线和有利的联盟。
To better manage their newly acquired
为了更好地管理新获得的
territories, [music] the British
领土，英国
Parliament passed the Quebec Act, which
议会通过了《魁北克法案》，该法案除
among other things expanded the borders
其他事项外，将
of [music] the province of Quebec
魁北克省的边界
southward into the Ohio Valley, placing
向南扩展到俄亥俄河谷，将
much of the Old Northwest under Quebec's
旧西北的大部分地区置于魁北克的
administration.
管辖之下。
This included areas that today make up
这其中包括如今构成
the states of Ohio, Indiana, Illinois,
俄亥俄州、印第安纳州、伊利诺伊州
and Michigan, among others.
和密歇根州等州的地区。
By expanding Quebec's borders [music]
通过将魁北克的疆界（音乐）扩展
deep into the North American interior,
到北美内陆深处，
much of what would later become the
后来成为
American Midwest was, on paper, governed
美国中西部的大部分地区，在纸面上，都曾是
as part of a British colony that would
英国殖民地的一部分，而这片殖民地
go on to form a core part of modern
后来成为了现代加拿大的核心部分
Canada.
。
This wasn't a random decision, but was
这并非偶然的决定，而是
largely driven by an economic strategy
主要受
that aims to maintain and profit from
旨在维持
the existing fur trade.
现有毛皮贸易并从中获利的经济战略驱动。
Previously, under French rule, the
此前，在法国统治下，该
region had been tied together through
地区通过
well-established trade networks and
完善的贸易网络​​和
alliances with indigenous nations.
与土著民族的联盟紧密联系在一起。
However, this caused immediate tension
然而，这立即引起了
among the 13 colonies, which had long
13个殖民地之间的紧张关系，这些殖民地长期以来一直将
viewed the Ohio Valley as a natural path
俄亥俄河谷视为
for [music] westward expansion. By
音乐向西传播的天然通道。
access, Britain fueled growing
英国将该地区置于魁北克的管辖之下，并限制殖民地的准入，这加剧了当地民众日益增长的
resentment. To many colonial Americans,
不满情绪。 对许多殖民地时期的美国人来说，《
the Quebec Act was far more than a mere
魁北克法案》远不止是一项简单的
boundary agreement. It was an attempt to
边界协议。 这是为了
limit their growth and influence, but it
限制他们的发展和影响力，但这不仅仅是
wasn't just about land. The Act also
关于土地的问题。 该法案还
carried various cultural implications.
具有各种文化意义。
It allowed the continuation of French
它使得法国
civil law and even protected Catholic
民法得以延续，甚至保护了
institutions in Quebec, which alarmed
魁北克的天主教机构，这令
many of the Protestant colonists. To
许多新教殖民者感到震惊。 在
them, it appeared as if Britain was
他们看来，英国似乎是在牺牲他们的利益来
favoring the colonial French at their
偏袒法国殖民地
expense. It was in this environment that
。 正是在这种环境下，
tensions reached a boiling point. The
紧张局势达到了白热化阶段。
Quebec Act was condemned in the colonies
魁北克法案在殖民地遭到谴责，
and often grouped among the so-called
并经常被归入所谓的
Intolerable Acts, becoming one of the
不可容忍法案之列，成为
driving factors that eventually pushed
最终推动
the colonies toward open rebellion and
殖民地走向公开叛乱并
ultimately a bloody war.
最终爆发血腥战争的驱动因素之一。
And speaking of the United States early
说到美国早期
days,
历史，
this video is brought to you by World of
这段视频由《
Warships.
战舰世界》赞助播出。
2026 marks America's 250th anniversary,
2026 年是美国建国 250 周年，《
and World of Warships is celebrating
战舰世界》将举办“
with the Dawn of a Nation event, live
国家黎明”活动来庆祝这一盛事，活动将于
June 17th through June 15th.
6 月 15 日至 17 日期间在线举行。
It's a free-to-play naval combat game
这是一款免费海战游戏，
with hundreds of historically inspired
拥有数百艘以历史为灵感的
ships, beautiful updated water and
舰船、精美的更新水面和
weather effects, and new live service
天气效果，以及每月更新的全新在线服务
content every month.
内容。
Easy to jump into with friends. This is
很容易和朋友一起玩。 这正是该
the kind of heritage the event leans
活动所着重体现的传统
into.
。
The USS Constitution is still the
美国宪法号仍然是
world's oldest commissioned warship
世界上现役最古老的军舰
afloat. And here you get to battle
。 在这里，你可以体验
through history.
历史的战斗。
Earn exclusive rewards and celebrate the
赢取专属奖励，颂扬
spirit that changed the world. Redeem my
改变世界的精神。 使用我的
code USA250 and you unlock a million
代码 USA250，即可解锁一百万
credits. 7 days premium, 500 doubloons,
积分。  7 天高级账号，500 金币，
the stars and stripes camo, plus two
星条旗迷彩，以及两艘
premium American ships, the cruiser USS
美国高级舰船：巡洋舰“
Albany and destroyer USS Smith. And an
奥尔巴尼”号和驱逐舰“史密斯”号。 此外，
additional bonus for new players. Play
新玩家还有额外奖励。 进行
10 battles and pick a bonus ship, South
10 场战斗，并选择一艘奖励舰船：
Carolina, St. Louis, or Wickes. Click my
南卡罗来纳号、圣路易斯号或威克斯号。 点击
link in the description and use code
简介中的链接，使用代码
USA250,
USA250，
available for new or returning players
适用于主机平台的新玩家或回归玩家
on console. It's World of Warships:
。 这是《战舰世界：
Legends. [music]
传奇》。  [音乐] 据
It's believed that as many as 50,000
信，战争期间有多达 5 万人
people died over the course of the war.
丧生。
And in the end, the colonies managed to
最终，各殖民地取得了
emerge victorious, securing their
胜利，获得了
independence and forming the United
独立，并组成了
States.
美国。
With the war over, North America entered
战争结束后，北美
into a prolonged period of
进入了漫长的
transformation, and its boundaries would
转型期，在接下来的一个世纪里，它的边界将
be continuously redrawn over the next
不断被重新划分
century. Almost immediately after the
。
American Revolutionary War, peace
美国独立战争结束后不久，欧洲便
negotiations were scheduled to take
安排了和平谈判
place in Europe, which culminated in the
，最终签订了《
Treaty of Paris.
巴黎条约》。
American negotiators who traveled to
前往欧洲的美国谈判代表
Europe, including Benjamin Franklin,
，包括本杰明·富兰克林、
John Adams, and John Jay, went with one
约翰·亚当斯和约翰·杰伊，都怀着一个
ambitious goal in mind. [music]
雄心勃勃的目标。  [音乐]
To secure the Old Northwest and
为了确保旧西北地区的安全，并将
establish the Mississippi River as the
密西西比河确立为
western boundary of their newly formed
他们新成立的邦联的西部边界
confederation. But, this was an
。 但这确实是一个
incredibly bold demand. At the time,
极其大胆的要求。 当时，
Britain still had many forts and a lot
英国在大湖区仍然拥有许多堡垒和很大的
of influence throughout the Great Lakes
影响力
region. In theory, it could have
。 理论上，它本可以
attempted to retain [music] control of
尝试保留对旧西北地区的[音乐]控制权
the Old Northwest, which would have set
，这将使它
it on a trajectory to become part of
走上成为
modern Canada. However, surprisingly,
现代加拿大一部分的道路。 然而，出乎意料的是，
this is not the path they took. Under
他们并没有选择这条路。 根据
the terms of the treaty, Britain ceded
条约条款，英国将
the Old Northwest, known at the time as
当时被称为俄亥俄
the territory northwest of the River
河西北部地区的旧西北地区割让
Ohio, to the United States. The
给了美国。 该
agreement established the Mississippi
协议确定
River as the western boundary of the US
密西西比河为美国的西部边界，
and the Great Lakes as the northern
五大湖为北部
boundary. The region included the land
边界。 该地区包括
west of Pennsylvania, northwest of the
宾夕法尼亚州以西、
Ohio River, and east of the Mississippi
俄亥俄河以北、密西西比河以东的土地
River. It comprised present-day Ohio,
。 它包括今天的俄亥俄州、
Indiana, Illinois, Michigan, Wisconsin,
印第安纳州、伊利诺伊州、密歇根州、威斯康星州
and part of Minnesota. But, why did the
和明尼苏达州的一部分。 但是，为什么历史上
most powerful empire ever to exist
最强大的帝国
refuse to try and hold on to the Old
拒绝尝试保住旧
Northwest, especially considering how
西北地区，尤其是考虑到
lucrative the trade networks in the
该地区的贸易网络
region were?
是多么有利可图？
Well, the answer is quite simple. It was
答案很简单。 它
exhausted from the war. This was both
因战争而疲惫不堪。 这既令人
shocking and humiliating. The loss of
震惊又令人羞辱。 失去
the 13 colonies wasn't just symbolic. It
13个殖民地不仅仅是象征性的。 这对
military blow to the empire. Looking at
帝国来说是一次严重的政治、经济和军事打击。
it from this angle, it's easy to see why
从这个角度来看，很容易理解为什么
Britain didn't want to fight over the
英国不想为
more distant and sparsely populated Old
更遥远、人口稀少的旧
Northwest. It simply wasn't worth it. By
西北地区而战。 根本不值得。
ceding the Old Northwest, British
英国官员希望通过割让旧西北地区来
officials hoped it would avoid any
避免任何
further conflict and, more importantly,
进一步的冲突，更重要的是，
preserve stable trade relations with the
维持与
newly formed US confederation. But,
新成立的美国邦联的稳定贸易关系。 但是，
there There
其中也存在
some geopolitical concerns. By granting
一些地缘政治方面的担忧。 英国给予
the US relatively generous borders,
美国相对宽松的边界，
Britain hoped this would form a stable
希望以此建立稳定的
relationship and potentially prevent the
关系，并有可能阻止
Americans from forming any kind of
美国
alliance with their long-time rival,
与其长期对手
France. Looking back, it's not hard to
法国结成任何形式的联盟。 回首往事，不难
imagine a reality where things were
想象，如果当时的情况有所
different. If British politicians had
不同会是什么样子。 如果英国政客
taken a tougher stance, [music] they
采取更强硬的立场，他们
might have drawn the new border at the
可能会把新的边界划在
Appalachian Mountains or even the Ohio
阿巴拉契亚山脉，甚至俄亥俄
River. In this hypothetical scenario,
河。 在这种假设情景下，
the Old Northwest would have remained
旧西北地区将继续作为
part of British North America and over
英属北美的一部分，并且随着
time might have even been incorporated
时间的推移，甚至可能在
less than a century later. This would
不到一个世纪后加拿大建国时被并入加拿大。 这将对
balance of power in North America.
北美的权力平衡产生严重后果。
What we know as the United States could
我们现在所知的美国原本可能面积
have been a lot smaller and more
小得多，而且更
confined to the east, [music] whereas
局限于东部，而
Canada would have controlled the Great
加拿大则可能控制
Lakes and a lot of the continent's
五大湖区和北美大陆的大部分
interior land.
内陆地区。
But in the end, the Americans managed to
但最终，美国人还是成功了，
pull it off and with the stroke of a
仅凭一
pen, much of the territory that would be
纸法令，
later called the Midwest fell under the
后来被称为中西部的大部分地区就落入了
dominion of the United States. But in
美国的统治之下。 但在
the wake of this, a new problem emerged.
此之后，又出现了一个新问题。
How did they plan to keep it? Towards
他们打算如何保住它？
the end of the 18th century, the United
18 世纪末，
States technically owned the Old
美国在名义上拥有了旧
Northwest, but it lacked the resources
西北地区，但
to actually control it. On paper, the
实际上却缺乏控制该地区的资源。 从法律意义上讲，这片
land was theirs, but in reality, several
土地是他们的，但实际上，
problems existed, many of which started
存在着许多问题，其中许多问题开始
to threaten their control over the
威胁到他们对该
region. The Native American tribes
地区的控制。
living in the region, such as the Miami,
居住在该地区的美洲原住民部落，如迈阿密人、
Shawnee, Lenape, and Wyandot, rejected
肖尼人、勒纳佩人和怀安多特人，拒绝接受《
the terms of the Treaty of Paris. From
巴黎条约》的条款。 在
their perspective, the British had no
他们看来，英国人没有
right to give away their land. This
权利出卖自己的土地。 这
resulted in the the
导致了
of the Western Confederacy, a powerful
西部联盟的成立，这是一个强大的
military alliance that resisted American
军事联盟，抵抗美国的
expansion. At the same time, Britain
扩张。 与此同时，英国并
hadn't entirely removed its presence
没有完全撤出
from the area. The empire continued to
该地区。 帝国继续占领
in the Old Northwest, such as Mackinac,
旧西北地区的几个战略要塞，如麦基诺堡、
Niagara, and Detroit. From these bases
尼亚加拉堡和底特律堡。 英国人从这些作战基地向
Western Confederacy with both arms and
西部联盟提供武器
ammunition, hoping to maintain a buffer
弹药，希望在
state between Canada and the US.
加拿大和美国之间维持一个缓冲国。
Another major problem they faced was
他们面临的另一个主要问题是
structural. At the time, the federal
结构性的。 当时，由于《邦联条例》的限制，联邦政府
government had no power to implement a
无权实施
system of taxation due to the Articles
税收制度
of Confederation.
。
While it could request funds from the
虽然它可以向各州请求拨款
states, they weren't compelled to pay.
，但各州没有义务支付。
As a result, there was a lack of
因此，缺乏
reliable revenue, meaning there was no
可靠的收入来源，这意味着没有
money to fund a standing army that could
资金来资助一支能够
defend the frontier. A breakthrough came
保卫边境的常备军。
in 1787 with the Northwest Ordinance,
1787 年的《西北法令》取得了突破性进展，该法令被
widely considered as one of the most
广泛认为是美国历史
important yet overlooked laws in
上最重要但却被忽视的法律之一
American history.
。
This ordinance created a system for
这项法令建立了一套将
transforming the western lands into
西部土地转变为
fully equal states, which meant they
完全平等的州的制度，这意味着它们
would no longer be treated as distant
将不再被视为遥远的
colonies, but as integral parts of the
殖民地，而是被视为美国不可分割的一部分
United States.
。
This paves the way for more migration to
这将为更多移民涌入
the region and better governance. The
该地区和改善治理铺平道路。 该
ordinance also banned slavery in the
法令还禁止该
region, which helped shape its social
地区的奴隶制，这有助于塑造该地区的社会
and political character, and public
和政治特征，并促进了与原州类似的公共
education and legal structures that
教育和法律结构的发展
were also promoted.
。
In effect, what would become the
实际上，后来成为
American Midwest wasn't just claimed, it
美国中西部的地区不仅被占领，而且还被
was systematically integrated into the
系统地融入了
United States.
美国。
But it still needed to be protected.
但它仍然需要保护。
After all, migration to the region
毕竟，
wouldn't help if the new settlers were
如果新移民
constantly attacked by the Western
不断受到西部
Confederacy.
联盟的攻击，那么迁徙到该地区也无济于事。
These challenges, along with other
这些挑战，以及其他
political and financial issues, helped
政治和金融问题，
drive the creation of the United States
推动了美国
Constitution and established a much
宪法的制定，并建立了一个更
stronger federal government that had the
强大的联邦政府，该政府
authority to collect taxes, regulate
有权征税、监管
trade, and ultimately raise and support
贸易，并最终组建和支持
armies. This was a major shift as now
军队。 这是一个重大转变，因为现在
the government could fund military
政府可以资助军事
projects, build forts, and properly
项目、修建堡垒，并
enforce its authority in the western
在西部地区切实行使权力
territories. American control was
。  1812 年
further solidified after the War of
战争后，美国的统治地位进一步巩固。
1812. During the war, the American
战争期间，
forces dealt a major blow to the Native
美军重创了
American Confederacy led by Tecumseh,
由特库姆塞领导的美洲原住民联盟，特库姆塞
whose death in 1813 marked a turning
于 1813 年去世，这标志着一个
point. The following year, the Treaty of
转折点。 次年，
Ghent was signed with both sides
双方签署了《根特条约》，
agreeing to return to pre-war borders.
同意恢复战前边界。
Had the United States failed to overcome
如果美国未能克服
these challenges or even to populate the
这些挑战，甚至未能迅速开发这片
territory quickly, the story of the
领土，那么中西部的故事
Midwest might have been different. A
或许就会有所不同。
sparsely populated frontier could have
人口稀少的边境地区可能
appeared vulnerable, inviting Britain to
显得不堪一击，从而诱使英国
reassert influence over the region from
从北方重新控制该地区
the north. It could have also become a
。 它也可能成为一个
buffer state, neither American nor
缓冲国，既不是美国也不是
Canadian, but somewhere in between.
加拿大，而是介于两者之间。
Today, the Midwest is one of the United
如今，中西部是
States' largest and most [music]
美国最大、最
important national regions, comprising
重要的音乐地区之一，它位于美国
12 states in the north central part of
中北部，由 12 个州组成
the nation, it serves as a central hub
，是
between the east and west coasts. In the
东西海岸之间的中心枢纽。
end, it wasn't just one moment that
最终，
decided the fate of the Midwest, but
决定中西部命运的并非某一刻，而是
instead a series of political choices,
一系列政治选择、
military wars, and economic priorities
军事战争和经济优先事项，
that all worked in America's favor,
所有这些都对美国有利，
shaping the North American map as we
塑造了我们
know it today.
今天所知的北美版图。
If you'd like to help us keep creating
如果您想帮助我们继续创作，
and get early access to our videos,
并提前观看我们的视频、
[music]
[音乐]
behind-the-scenes content, and other
幕后内容和其他
perks, consider becoming a member right
福利，请考虑在
here on YouTube or joining us on
YouTube 上成为会员，或在 Patreon 上加入我们
Patreon. Every bit of support helps. And
。 每一份支持都至关重要。
as always, thank you so much for
一如既往，非常感谢您的
watching.
收看。